https://emssurg.com/privacy-policy/

Website Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our visitors. We only collect personal information as is needed to provide the information, service, or assistance you request.
Information Collected
If you visit our website to browse, read, or download information:
Your web browser automatically sends us (and we may retain) information such as the:
Internet domain through which you access the Internet;
Internet Protocol address of the computer you are using;
type of browser software and operating system you are using;
date and time you access our site; and
the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our site.
We will use this information to help us maintain this site, e.g., to determine the number of visitors to different pages of our site, to ensure the site is working properly, and to help us make our site more accessible and useful to visitors.
We will not use this information to identify individuals, except for site security or law enforcement purposes.
We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide personal information via online forms.
We will collect (and may retain) any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address, and phone number, and any other information you provide. We will use this information to try to fulfill your request and may use it provide you with additional information at a later time. We will not disclose such information to third parties, except as specified in this privacy policy.
How Long We Keep Information
We may keep information that will collect for an unlimited period of time.
Security
Please note that electronic communication, particularly email, is not necessarily secure against interception. Please do not send sensitive data (e.g., Social Security, bank account, or credit card numbers) by email or web form.
Cookies
We may use cookies in order to customize this site for return visitors.  These cookies are not required for site functionality.  Additionally, third-party widgets such as YouTube or Flickr may install cookies depending on their configuration.  You are not required to accept any cookies to use this site.
Google Analytics
We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
PayPal Payment Processing
We use Paypal for ecommerce payment processing. When you purchase a product through our website you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to Paypal for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy.
Product CategoriesSurgical Bras
Compression Garments
Specialty Tops
Binders
Other
Breast Separator
Abdominal Binders
CartContact Us:
Phone: 570-374-0569
Phone or Fax: 800-635-7437 or 800-409-3188
E-mail: emssurg@verizon.net
Doctors / Surgery Centers
Call for special pricing.
Hours of Operation:
Monday-Friday 8am-4pm EST
Address:
801 North Old Trail
Selinsgrove, Pa 17870
Scroll to top
